<featureType>
  <id>FeatureTypeInfoImpl--4019d23:14dd2e9815d:-7fd8</id>
  <name>MB_EXTRACT_SAMPLE_INVERTEBRATE_ALL_MAP</name>
  <nativeName>MB_EXTRACT_SAMPLE_INVERTEBRATE_ALL_MAP</nativeName>
  <namespace>
    <id>NamespaceInfoImpl--558bdc10:1485b268ab8:7c25</id>
  </namespace>
  <title>Condition of rocky reef communities around Tasmania: invertebrate surveys (map only)</title>
  <abstract>The data is the quantitative abundance of megafaunal invertebrates derived from underwater visual census methods involving transect counts at rocky reef sites around Tasmania. This data forms part of a larger dataset that also surveyed fish abundance and algal cover for the area. The aggregated dataset allows examination of changes in Tasmanian shallow reef floral and faunal communities over a decadal scale - initial surveys were conducted in 1992-1995, and again at the same sites in 2006-2007. There are plans for ongoing surveys.&#xd;
&#xd;
An additional component was added in the latter study - a boat ramp study looking at the proximity of boat ramps and their effects of fishing. We analysed underwater visual census data on fishes and macroinvertebrates (abalone and rock lobsters) at 133 shallow rocky reef sites around Tasmania that ranged from 0.6 - 131 km from the nearest boat ramp. These sites were not all the same as those used for the comparison of 1994 and 2006 reef communities. The subset of 133 sites examined in this component consisted of only those sites that were characterized by the two major algal (kelp) types (laminarian or fucoid dominated). Sites with atypical algal assemblages were omitted from the 196 sites surveyed in 2006.&#xd;
&#xd;
This study aimed to examine reef community data for changes at the community level, changes in species richness and introduced species populations, and changes that may have resulted from ocean warming and fishing.&#xd;
&#xd;
The methods are described in detail in Edgar and Barrett (1997). Primarily the data are derived from transects at 5 m depth and/or 10 m depth at each site surveyed. The underwater visual census (UVC) methodology used to survey rocky reef communities was designed to maximise detection of (i) changes in population numbers and size-structure (ii) cascading ecosystem effects associated with disturbances such as fishing, (iii) long term change and variability in reef assemblages.&#xd;
&#xd;
***NOTE THIS LAYER PROVIDES A MAPPING VISUALISATION ONLY***</abstract>
  <keywords>
    <string>features</string>
    <string>MB_EXTRACT_SAMPLE_INVERTEBRATE_ALL_MAP</string>
  </keywords>
  <metadataLinks>
    <metadataLink>
      <type>text/plain</type>
      <metadataType>19139</metadataType>
      <content>http://metadata.imas.utas.edu.au/geonetwork/srv/en/metadata.show?uuid=9aee213b-ab23-4321-9994-f7db2f6b2e78</content>
    </metadataLink>
  </metadataLinks>
  <nativeCRS>GEOGCS[&quot;WGS 84&quot;, 
  DATUM[&quot;World Geodetic System 1984&quot;, 
    SPHEROID[&quot;WGS 84&quot;, 6378137.0, 298.257223563, AUTHORITY[&quot;EPSG&quot;,&quot;7030&quot;]], 
    AUTHORITY[&quot;EPSG&quot;,&quot;6326&quot;]], 
  PRIMEM[&quot;Greenwich&quot;, 0.0, AUTHORITY[&quot;EPSG&quot;,&quot;8901&quot;]], 
  UNIT[&quot;degree&quot;, 0.017453292519943295], 
  AXIS[&quot;Geodetic longitude&quot;, EAST], 
  AXIS[&quot;Geodetic latitude&quot;, NORTH], 
  AUTHORITY[&quot;EPSG&quot;,&quot;4326&quot;]]</nativeCRS>
  <srs>EPSG:4326</srs>
  <nativeBoundingBox>
    <minx>143.828307105</minx>
    <maxx>148.458024071</maxx>
    <miny>-43.644509362</miny>
    <maxy>-39.213839485</maxy>
    <crs>EPSG:4326</crs>
  </nativeBoundingBox>
  <latLonBoundingBox>
    <minx>143.828307105</minx>
    <maxx>148.458024071</maxx>
    <miny>-43.644509362</miny>
    <maxy>-39.213839485</maxy>
    <crs>EPSG:4326</crs>
  </latLonBoundingBox>
  <projectionPolicy>FORCE_DECLARED</projectionPolicy>
  <enabled>true</enabled>
  <advertised>true</advertised>
  <metadata>
    <entry key="elevation">
      <dimensionInfo>
        <enabled>false</enabled>
      </dimensionInfo>
    </entry>
    <entry key="time">
      <dimensionInfo>
        <enabled>false</enabled>
        <defaultValue/>
      </dimensionInfo>
    </entry>
    <entry key="cachingEnabled">false</entry>
  </metadata>
  <store class="dataStore">
    <id>DataStoreInfoImpl--558bdc10:1485e0de12a:-4ad7</id>
  </store>
  <serviceConfiguration>false</serviceConfiguration>
  <maxFeatures>0</maxFeatures>
  <numDecimals>0</numDecimals>
  <padWithZeros>false</padWithZeros>
  <forcedDecimal>false</forcedDecimal>
  <overridingServiceSRS>false</overridingServiceSRS>
  <skipNumberMatched>false</skipNumberMatched>
  <circularArcPresent>false</circularArcPresent>
</featureType>